https://www.gworks.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentPrivacy PolicyUpdated: October 27, 2020IntroductionGIS
Workshop, LLC, doing business as gWorks (“Company” or “We” or “Us” or “Our”),
respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance
with this policy.This
policy applies to our websites, our web-based and mobile apps, and our
products, services, and features (our “Services”)
and describes our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and
disclosing information when you use the Services.This policy applies to information we
collect:On our website, gworks.com.On our mobile applications.On our County WebGIS application.On our SimpleCity Cloud and Desktop applications.On our FrontDesk and FrontDesk Add-on applications.On our custom applications.In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and us.When
you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and
services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.This policy does not apply to
information collected by:Us offline or on
any other website operated by any third party; orAny third party,
including through any application or content (including advertising) that may
link to or be accessible from or on the Website.Please
read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding
your information and how we will treat it. BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SERVICES,
YOU AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.  IF YOU
DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT ACCESS THE SERVICES.Information We CollectThe
information we may collect through our Services includes:PERSONAL INFORMATIONPersonally
identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you.
Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your
email address, name, phone number, postal address, and other information
(“personal information”). We collect this information for the purpose of
providing the Services, identifying and communicating with you, responding to
your requests/inquiries, and improving our services.PAYMENT INFORMATIONPayment
information, such as data related to your payment method (e.g. valid credit
card number, card brand, expiration date) that we may collect when you
purchase, order, return, exchange our products, or request information about
our Services.OTHER INFORMATIONInformation about
your internet connection, the equipment you use to access the Services, and
usage details, including IP address, browser type, operating system, access
times, and the pages you viewed directly before and after accessing the Services.How We Collect Your InformationWe collect
information from and about users of our Services:Directly from you
when you provide it to us.Automatically
when you use the Services.Information You Provide To UsWe collect information you
provide directly to us, for example, when you create an account, participate in
interactive features of the Services (such as online chat or message boards),
fill out a form, respond to a survey, request customer support, or otherwise
communicate with us via the Services.  Such information may include
personal information, payment information, and any other information you choose
to provide.Information We Collect Automatically When You Use The ServicesWhen you access or use the
Services, we automatically collect information about you, including the
following:We log information about your use of the
Services, including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed,
your IP address, and the page you visited before and after navigating to the
Services.We use various technologies to collect
information, including sending cookies to your computer or mobile device and
placing web beacons on pages of the Services.Cookies
are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that help us
to improve the Services and your experience, see which areas and features of
the Services are popular, and count visits. Most browsers are set to accept
cookies by default.Web
beacons are small electronic files (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags,
and single-pixel gifs) that permit us, for example, to count users who have
visited those pages and for other related Services statistics (for example,
recording the popularity of certain Services content and verifying system and
server integrity).We may also
partner with selected third-party vendors, such as Google Analytics, to allow
tracking technologies and remarketing services on the Services through the use
of first party cookies and third-party cookies to, among other things, analyze
and track users’ use of the Services, determine the popularity of certain
content, and better understand online activity. By accessing the Services, you
consent to the collection and use of your information by these third-party
vendors. You are encouraged to review their respective privacy policies and
contact them directly for responses to your questions. We do not transfer
personal information to these third-party vendors. However, if you do not want
any information to be collected and used by tracking technologies, you can
visit the third-party vendor’s website or Network Advertising Initiative
Opt-Out Tool or Digital Advertising Alliance Opt-Out Tool.How We Use Your InformationWe use information that we
collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal
information, to:Provide you with the Services and their
contents, and any other information, products, or services that you request
from us.Fulfill any other purpose for which you provide
it.Give you notices about your account.Carry out our obligations and enforce our rights
arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for
billing and collection.Notify you when Services updates are available,
and of changes to any products or services we offer or provide though it.The usage information we collect helps us to
improve our Services and to deliver a better and more personalized experience
by enabling us to:Estimate
our audience size and usage patterns.Store
information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Services
according to your individual interests.Speed
up your searches.Recognize
you when you use the Services.We may also use your
information to contact you about our own and third parties’ goods and services
that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information
in this way, please adjust your user preferences in your account profile. For
more information, see “CHOICES ABOUT HOW WE USE AND DISCLOSE YOUR
INFORMATION” .We may use the information we
collect to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences. Even
though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without
your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the
advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.Disclosure of Your InformationWe may disclose aggregated
information about our users, and information that does not identify any
individual or device, without restriction.In addition, we may disclose
personal information that we collect or you provide:To our subsidiaries and affiliates.To contractors, service providers, and other
third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual
obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the
purposes for which we disclose it to them.To a buyer or other successor in the event of a
merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale
or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part
of a bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal
information held by us about our Services users is among the assets
transferred.To third parties to market their products or
services to you if you have not opted out of these disclosures.  For more information, see “CHOICES ABOUT
HOW WE USE AND DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION” .To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.For any other purpose disclosed by us when you
provide the information.With your consent.To comply with any court order, law, or legal
process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.To enforce our rights arising from any contracts
entered into between you and us, including the Terms of Use, and for billing
and collection.If we believe
disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or
safety of us, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information
with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and
credit risk reduction.Your Choices About Our Collection, Use, and Disclosure of Your InformationWe strive to provide you with
choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. This section
describes mechanisms we provide for you to control certain uses and disclosures
of your information.Tracking Technologies. You can set your browser to refuse all or
some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you
disable or refuse cookies, some parts of the Services may then be inaccessible
or not function properly.Location Information. You can choose whether or not to allow the Services
to collect and use real-time information about your device’s location through
the device’s privacy settings. If you block the use of location information,
some parts of the Services may then be inaccessible or not function properly.Promotion by us. If you do not want us to use your email address to
promote our own or third parties’ products or services, you can opt-out by
logging into the Services and adjusting your user preferences in your account
profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending us an email
stating your request to info@gworks.com.  Targeted Advertising by us. If you do not want us to use
information that we collect or that you provide to us to deliver advertisements
according to our advertisers’ target-audience preferences, you can opt-out in
your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending
us an email stating your request to info@gworks.com.Disclosure of Your Information for Third-Party Advertising and
Marketing. If you do not want us to share your personal information with
unaffiliated or non-agent third parties for advertising and marketing purposes,
you can opt-out by logging into the Services and adjusting your user
preferences in your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant
boxes or by sending us an email stating your request to info@gworks.com.We do not control third parties’
collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising.
However these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have
your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving
targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative
(“NAI”) on the NAI’s website.Third-Party WebsitesThe Services may contain links to
third-party websites and applications of interest, including advertisements and
external services, that are not affiliated with us. Once you have used these
links to leave the Services, any information you provide to these third parties
is not covered by this Privacy Policy, and we cannot guarantee the safety and
privacy of your information. Before visiting and providing any information to
any third-party websites, you should inform yourself of the privacy policies
and practices (if any) of the third party responsible for that website, and
should take those steps necessary to, in your discretion, protect the privacy
of your information. We are not responsible for the content, privacy and
security practices, or policies of any third parties, including other websites,
services, or applications that may be linked to or from the Services.Your California Privacy RightsCalifornia Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about categories of personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared personal information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to us using the contact information provided below.If you are under 18 years of age,
reside in California, and have a registered account with the Services, you have
the right to request removal of unwanted data that you publicly post on the
Services. To request removal of such data, please contact us using the contact
information provided below, and include the email address associated with your
account and a statement that you reside in California.  We will make sure the data is not publicly
displayed on the Services, but please be aware that the data may not be
completely or comprehensively removed from our systems.  Accessing and Correcting Your Personal InformationYou can review and change your personal information by logging into the Services
and visiting your account profile page.
You may also send us an email at info@gworks.com to request access to, correct, or delete any personal information that
you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by
also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change
information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement
or cause the information to be incorrect.Data SecurityWe have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information
from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and
disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers
behind firewalls. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL
technology.The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we
have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain
parts of our Services, you are responsible for keeping this password
confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet and
mobile platforms is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect
your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal
information transmitted through our Services. Any transmission of personal
information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of
any privacy settings or security measures we provide.Send “Do Not Track” SignalsSome browsers have incorporated
“Do Not Track” (DNT) features that can send a signal to the websites you visit
indicating you do not wish to be tracked. Because there is not yet a common
understanding of how to interpret the DNT signal, our Services do not currently
respond to browser DNT signals. You can use the range of other tools we provide
to control data collection and use, including the ability to opt out of receiving
marketing from us as described above.Policy for ChildrenWe do not knowingly solicit
information from or market to children under the age of 13. If you are under
13, do not use or provide any information through the Services or on or through
any of their features.  If you become
aware of any data we have collected from children under age 13, please contact
us using the contact information provided below.  If we learn we have collected or received
personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental
consent, we will delete that information.Changes to Our Privacy PolicyWe reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time
and for any reason.  We will alert you
about any changes by updating the “Updated” date shown at the top of this
Privacy Policy.  Any changes or
modifications will be effective immediately upon posting the updated Privacy
Policy on the Services, and you waive the right to receive specific notice of
each such change or modification. You are encouraged to periodically review
this Privacy Policy to stay informed of updates. You will be deemed to have
been made aware of, will be subject to, and will be deemed to have accepted the
changes in any revised Privacy Policy by your continued use of the Services
after the date such revised Privacy Policy is posted.GDPR NoticeIn compliance with the European
Union (“EU”) General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), we may rely upon one
or more legal bases defined in the GDPR to collect, use, share and otherwise
process the personal information of individual located in the EU, including
where:Necessary to perform a contract we have with
you, such as our terms of engagement, and to provide services;You have consented to the processing (in which
case you may revoke your consent at any time);Necessary for us to comply with a legal
obligation, or to establish, exercise or defend legal claims;Necessary to protect your vital interests or
those of others;Necessary in the public interest; andNecessary for the purposes of our or a third
party’s legitimate interests, such as those of clients, partners, staff or
others, provided that those interests are not overridden by your interests or
fundamental rights and freedoms.Where we collect, use, disclose
and otherwise process your information based on legitimate interests, we may
rely on the following interests:Provision of services: We use your information
to provide services to you and others.Keeping our services safe and secure: We use
your information in certain instances as necessary to pursue our and your
legitimate interests of keeping some of our services, such as our domains,
websites, apps, offices and events, safe and secure. For example, we collect IP
addresses to ensure our website and apps are not subject to fraudulent access.Marketing our services: We use your information
as necessary to pursue our legitimate interests in marketing our services.Providing, improving and developing services: We
use your information as necessary to pursue our legitimate interests in
tailoring and improving our services. For example, if you are a customer, we
may send you a survey or questionnaire to understand your experience in
obtaining services from us.Providing seamless services with our affiliates:
In some cases, the services require the engagement of, or sharing of your
information with, other companies affiliated with us.If you are located in the EU,
under certain circumstances, you may have certain legal rights under the GDPR,
including:To access the personal data we maintain about
youTo receive information about how we process your
personal dataTo correct your personal dataTo have your personal data erasedTo object to or restrict how we process your
personal dataTo request your personal data be transferred to
a third partyTo withdraw any consent you may have given us to
process your personal dataIf you are an EU resident, you
have the right to object to our processing that is based on legitimate
interests by contacting us at the address or number below. If you are located
in the EU and you believe that we have infringed your rights under the GDPR,
please contact us by sending an email to info@gworks.com or calling us at: (888) 608-7666.You have the right to lodge a
complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in your applicable Member
State.Contact InformationYou
have the right to access, correct, and delete inaccuracies in your personal
information and privacy preferences on the Services at any time by signing into
your account and editing your personal information in your account
profile.  You may also do so by
contacting us via telephone, postal mail, or email.  If you have questions or comments about this
Privacy Policy and our privacy practices, please contact us at:GIS Workshop, LLC dba gWorks3905 S. 148th St., Ste 200, Omaha, NE 68144(888) 608-7666; info@gworks.comHomeSolutionsCompanyResourcesContact
MenuHomeSolutionsCompanyResourcesContact
Twitter
Facebook-f
Linkedin
888-608-7666
info@gworks.com
3905 South 148th St, Ste 200
Omaha, NE 68144
Close Menu HomeSolutionsSimpleCityFrontDeskCounty WebGISProfessional ServicesSupport ServicesCompanyCareersTeamResourcesEventsgWorks UniversityTestimonialsBlogCOVID-19 ResourcesMarket SquareContact
